import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet4: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "___ enables two parties in different locations to see and speak to each other?",
    "options": [
      "Telephone",
      "Teleconferencing",
      "Messenger chat",
      "Television"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Business reports must use ___ nouns",
    "options": [
      "Concrete",
      "Abstract",
      "Proper",
      "Common"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Business letters are used primarily to communicate with ___",
    "options": [
      "External stakeholders",
      "Internal stakeholders",
      "customers",
      "agents"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "The ___ is often interpreted as a lack of understanding or attention.",
    "options": [
      "Noise",
      "Silence",
      "Yawning",
      "disturbance"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Shareholders are very important internal stakeholders since they are the ___ of the company",
    "options": [
      "Managers",
      "Owners",
      "Directors",
      "Union Members"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "In the listening process, the ___ stage occurs as the audience categorizes and retains the information they have gathered from the speaker for future access.",
    "options": [
      "Evaluating",
      "Understanding",
      "remembering",
      "responding"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "___ is a great way to get a broad idea of the topic being discussed.",
    "options": [
      "Skimming",
      "Scanning",
      "Extensive",
      "Intensive"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "The pleasurable emotional reaction of happiness in response to a fulfilment of a desire of goal is defined as ___",
    "options": [
      "chemical reaction",
      "self-reflection",
      "gratification",
      "mindfulness"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "___ communication is a strategy covering the wide range of methods companies use to capture the attention of the public.",
    "options": [
      "Internal",
      "external",
      "lateral",
      "downward"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "M in MAN stands for ___",
    "options": [
      "manual",
      "metropolitan",
      "meter",
      "madras"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
